Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, 1885-2017 and undated RL.00963
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- PHOTOGRAPHS AND NEGATIVES SERIES, 1920s-1980s
  - Photographs and Negatives Not Entered into the ROAD Database Subseries
    - Miscellaneous Negatives
      - OAAA Negatives (Box PN78)
        - Columbus Outdoor Advertising Company
          - Negatives from Numbered Folders, 19 folders (Box PN78)
          - Unnumbered Black/White Negatives, 1930s-1950s, 35 folders (Box PN78)
          - Unnumbered Color Negatives, 1940s-1970s, 13 folders (Box PN78)
          - Unsorted Negatives, 9 folders (Box PN78)
        - Criterion Advertising
          - Black/White, undated (Folders 1-14 of 28), Folders 1-14 of 28 (Box PN78)
          - Black/White, undated, Folders 15-28 of 28 (Box PN79)
          - Color, undated, 5 folders (Box PN79)
          - Duplicates (Box PN79)
          - Numbered Negatives, 2 folders (Box PN79)
            [Numbered 1-227]
        - Eller Outdoor
          - Index to 1970s Negatives (Box PN79)
          - Negatives (Box PN79)
            [Marked Book 1]
        - Eller/Pacific
          - Miscellaneous Negative, undated, 2 folders (Box PN79)
        - Foster & Kleiser
          - Binder 1, 23 folders (Box PN79)
            [Numbered FK 200-271]
          - Binder 2, 48 folders (Box PN80)
            [Numbered FK 1-199]
          - Miscellaneous, 1940s, 35 folders (Box PN80)
          - Miscellaneous, undated, 7 folders (Box PN80)
        - Other Negatives
          - Poster Advertising Association, Directors, 1921 (Box PN80)
          - Volkswagen, undated (Box PN80)
        - Foster & Kleiser Negatives, undated (Box PN81)
    - Thomas Cusack Company: See Cusack, Thomas (Box PN81)
  - Negatives Removed from PN1-PN62
    - AAA0035-AAA1137 (Box PN82)
    - AAA2470-AAA3768 (Box PN83)
    - AAA7729-AAA7931 (Box PN84)
    - AAA8272-AAA9999, BBB0001-BBB0151 (Box PN85)
    - BBB0944-BBB1223 (Box PN86)
    - BBB1360-BBB1746 (Box PN87)
    - BBB1747-BBB2256 (Box PN88)
    - BBB2257-BBB3325 (Box PN89)
    - BBB4783-BBB6789 (Box PN90)
    - Miscellaneous nitrate negatives (Box PN91)
    - Miscellaneous nitrate negatives (Box PN92)
- PHYSICAL STRUCTURE SERIES, 1920-1987
  The series contains information on: technologies; the development of billboard structures; research and solutions to a variety of construction problems; building codes and standards; research on color, paint, paper, and pasting techniques; illumination techniques; and alternative billboard designs. Also the series pertains to the evolution of billboard structures, in particular the Loewy panels designed after World War II, and the all-metal structures pioneered by the Tiffen Art Metal Co.
  - Aluminum and Steel (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    [See also Box PS14]
    - Alcoa Research on Aluminum, 1948-1950 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - ARMCO Research on Stainless, 1949-1952 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Bloede Research on Aluminum, 1947-1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Bloede Research on Stainless Steel, 1946-1950 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Comparing Aluminum, Galvanized and Black Iron Sheet, 1947, 2 folders (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Foster & Kleiser Stainless Steel Research, 1949-1951 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - General Outdoor Advertising Inspection of Stainless Steel Panel Moulding, 1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Metal Cleaner Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Metal Cleaner Research, 1948-1952 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - OAAA Aluminum Research, 1947-1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Stainless Steel Care and Maintenance, 1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Stainless Steel Research- Clarksburg, 1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Stainless Steel Research-Corrosion at Biloxi, 1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Stainless Steel Research-Naccanol Metal Cleaner, 1947-1949 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
      [Metal Cleaner-Naccanol: Stainless Steel Research (Naccanol is a detergent wetting agent) letters, brochure, report]
    - Steel Uprights in Cantilever Construction, 1950 July (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
  - Artwork, Lithography, and Printing
    - American Art Works Correspondence, 1946-1947 [Coshocton, Ohio] (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Art Exhibits, 1931-1935 and undated (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Artist- Harvey Simpson Bio., 1973-1991 (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
    - Billboard Art, 1967-1987, 3 folders (Box PS1 -Letter Size)
      [Office Records 1970s-Bicentennial Exhibit; HUD Seminar; OSHA Standards; Highway Beautification Commission, Etc, 1967-1989 Full; Billboard Art (news clippings; sign painters' art show); New West magazine article on art billboards; black and white article with color photo; Kodak--photo-evolution of painted billboards; spiral booklet of Patrick Media Group- 1987 Billboard Art Program; article-Pop billboards; 1981-1982 Outdoor Art Contest; correspondence; booklet-Arizona State U. Design competition; Horizon magazine- Art as big as All Outdoors; Sunset magazine- Los Angeles Art Walking; book- Art in America,1967-1987; Slides]
    - Catalog A-Wilson's Gummed Paper Letters and Figures, 1930 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Committee on Lithography, 1946 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      [Poster Sizes and Standards]
    - Day-Glo, undated (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Exhibition of Outdoor Advertising Art, Scrapbook, 1941 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Lithography-Assorted Companies, undated (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Lithography Miscellaneous, 1940 and undated (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Printing Procedure Inquiry, 1946-1957 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence; winter posting; junior panel; specifications; lye cooking poster paste; preparation of poster paste; Outdoor Advertising News,1949]
    - Printing-Rose Poster Printing, undated (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Printing- The National Group, undated (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - Spanger Brothers Catalog, ca. 1926, 2 folders (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      [(Hand labeled)- Olli-Please use photographed: 70 pages-du House-$75 first copy, $50 second copy, Geil Graphics-$300 first copy, $122 second copy; (photographs of book pages-Spanger Bros., Newark, N.J. whole sign catalog pages 1-64); catalog of Spanger Bros.]
  - Building Code
    - American National Standards Institute, A60.1, Proposed Revisions, 1975 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
    - American Standards Association (ASA)
      - A60 Code Revision, 1952-1960 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - A60 Committee Reactivation, 1960-1962 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - B-2 Building Code, 1955-1962 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - Building Code and Construction Standards Correlating Committee, 1948-1951 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - Building Code Requirements for Signs and Outdoor Displays, Drawings, undated (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - Building Code Requirements for Signs and Outdoor Displays, 1941-1952 [Drafts on A60.1, 1949] (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box PS2 -Letter Size)
      - Standard Code Requirements, Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      - Standards, 1952 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
        [American Standard Building Requirements for Sign and Outdoor Display Structures ( ASA Standard is Model for Practical Sign Ordinance pasted on mounting board]
    - Building Officials Conference of America Basic Code, undated (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Construction Regulations, 1920s-1953 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Construction Regulations, 1943-1955 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Model Building Code: correspondence (plus Lima, Ohio Advertising Code)]
    - Model Building Code-A60.1, 1949, Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Sign Code, Ordinance, 1949-1958 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Specifications for Additions and Alterations to Existing Building, dated 1947 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - OAAA Revision of BOCA- Recommendations, ca. 1948 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
  - Color and Paint
    - Administrative Files-Paint Operations Workshop, 1953 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Presentations- Essentials of Design by Mark Steelen; Reproduction of Copy by A.R. Jordon; Animation and Embellishment Techniques by W.W. Miller]
    - Blue Samples, undated (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Blue Standard, 1939-1946 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Colors Added to Basic Chart Correspondence (1939-1944) - Glidden, Valentin & Company, Frost, O'Brian Varnish, Texlite]
    - Bulletin Color Conference, 1950 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence (Representatives and O.A.A.)]
    - Bulletin Color Conference, 1950 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence (Agency and Advertiser representative)]
    - Bulletin Color Conference (Manufacturers Correspondence), 1950 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Bulletin Colors, 1937-1939 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Basic Bulletin Colors (1936-1939), Color Charts and Samples, Correspondence (1939), Socony, Sherwin Williams, Roman, Alston Lucas, Dupont]
    - Bulletin Colors, Pamphlets, 1938-1957 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Color Charts, undated (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
    - Color Drift and Porcelain, 1950-1952 (Box PS3 -Letter Size)
      [Color Panel Selection-Bowles, 1952; correspondence, 1950; Fuller Tinting Guide; Duplex and O.A.A. basic color bulletins, 1950]
    - Color Drift Control, 1955-1956 and undated (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Color Drift Samples, 1952 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Samples (1956) Standard; Fuller paints, 1952-1956; Bowles; Sears & Roebuck; U.S. Steele]
    - Color Drift Samples, 1952 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Color Manual, 1946 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Color Permanency Classification, 1947 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Color Samples, 1950 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence-O.A.A. and Sherwin Williams; O.A.A. and Foster & Kleiser]
    - Color Selection, 1950 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Socony/ O.A.A. correspondence, Coca-Cola/ O.A.A. correspondence, Foster & Kleiser]
    - Color Selection, 1951 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Approval Correspondence- Glidden, Standard Oil, T.J. Roan, U.S. Color Card]
    - Color Spectrophotometer Graphs, 1950, 2 folders (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Green Paint, 1941-1956 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence-Foster Green Paint (color samples attached to correspondence)]
    - Inquiries on Statement of Policy, 1958 (file of Tom Carabine) (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Manufacturers, Correspondence, 1950 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Updating/ Samples- Glidden, Sherwin Williams]
    - Miscellaneous, 1950 and undated (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence Legibility-O.A.A. and Socony]
    - Nomenclature and Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [ 1950 Color Bulletin; correspondence O.A.A. and paint manufacturers concerning paint samples]
    - Paint Conference Planning Meeting, 1957 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Painted Bulletins, 1983 and undated (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Painted Display Basic Bulletin Colors, 1951 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Painted Panels, 1933-1955 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Panels-Painted reports; color chart; A Guide for the Preparation of Copy and Art for Painted Displays; Opportunity in National Painted Display Advertising--If... by John Paver]
    - Paints and Painting, 1941-1950 and undated (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Photo & negatives; rules; poster panel green; 1941-1950 meeting of the Painted Display Standards Subcommittee 1950; maintenance paint manual undated]
    - Peeling, 1955 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
    - Red and Blue Samples, 1948-1950 and undated (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Color--Basic Bulletin Covers; Color Samples-- DuPont, Sherwin Williams, etc.]
    - Sample Selection, 1950 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence-- Foster & Kleiser, Glidden Color Name Suggestions]
    - Spray Painting, 1941-1946 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Paints and Painting-Spray (reprint from OAAA News)]
    - Weathering Tests, 1950-1953 (Box PS4 -Letter Size)
      [Weatherometer Tests (correspondence, published reports from Atlas Electric Devices Company]
  - General Construction (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Akron Clinic Photos, 1949 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
      [(Photos-erecting billboard, workman using paint burning), Region 5, Akron GOA plant-vat of cooking paste, poster wetting tank; 1949 June Outdoor Advertising Association News]
    - Builder, Alabama Bearings, undated (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Construction-Concrete, 1943-1952 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Construction Images, 1929 and undated, 2 folders (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Construction, Wood A-Frame, 1951 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Engineering Design Manual, 1955 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
      [Poster Structures- Engineering Design Manual: Outdoor Advertising Structures]
    - Engineering Design Manual, 1964 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Engineering Recommendations, 1954 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Equipment, 1931-1952 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
      [Suppliers Conference Chicago, Ill. - 1955 Jan. 10]
    - Evaluation and Equipment, 1950-1956, undated (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Ghaster Construction, 1951 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Improvements, 1956-1957? (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
      [Improvement Trends; draft of-OAAA members 1958 Invest Millions for Capital Improvements in One Year]
    - Information Bulletins, 1941-1951 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Loewy and Associates, 1948-1952 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Loewy Panels, 1946-1953 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Loewy Panel Users, 1950-1951 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Loewy Plan for Improved Structural System, 1959-1960 (Box PS5 -Letter Size)
    - Maintenance and Improvement Manual, [1971], 2 folders (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Mechanical Action, undated (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1957 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Construction Photos, 1937-1949 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
      [Photos: Construction & Erection ( Pennsylvania, Seattle, Akron); K.L. (Karl) Ghaster ( 1940)-construction, with close-ups and tools; handwritten charts]
    - Officer Correspondence, 1941-1951 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Pamphlets, 1957, undated (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Painted Display Standards Meeting & Survey of Bulletin Standards, 1950-1951 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Panel Construction and Anchorage, 1944-1948 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
      [ 1946 Poster Panel and (Loewy design; standards; moulding; Permolite coating; tapered steel posts; porcelain enamel moulding; construction; wood or steel frames; Notre Dame tests; Texlite; blueprints)]
    - Panel Maintenance, 1945-1951 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
      [Panels-Maintenance (Improved poster green; slipperiness of walkway surfaces; care of stainless steel; galvanized sheet metal; rust prevention; soil condition and anchors)]
    - Panel Specifications (between 1918 and 1926) (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Plant Modernization, 1956 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Pole Type Building Design, 1957 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Posters, Miniature, 1958 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Poster Panel Miscellaneous, 1929-1952 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
      [Panels-Posters (correspondence; standard group poster panels; Tandem Twin Tubular Structure drawing)]
    - Poster Standardization and LNA Discussions, 1953 Oct., 2 folders (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Revised Construction, 1930 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Roof Structures, 1953 (Box PS6 -Letter Size)
    - Signs and Outdoor Advertising Structures, 1948 April (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Specifications, 1948-1956 and undated (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
      [Blue Prints Visualized: Standard Poster Panel]
    - Specifications of the 24, 30 sheet posters, 1961 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Specifications and Worksheets, [1920s] (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Speeches, 1945-1948 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standard Structure Types, 1939-1956 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standard Structures, 1926-1949 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
      [Panels; standard city and suburban bulletin; imprint; mechanical drawing; increase of illuminate panels; apron, lattice and embellishment; photos]
    - Standard Structures, 1939 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standard Structures, Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standards, 1956 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standards Book, Drawings, 1949-1956 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standards for Equipment, 1940 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standards--Imprint, 1949-1952 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standards of Practice, ca. [1963] (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Standards--Standard Structures Pamphlet, 1939-1956 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
      [Projects--Standard Structures Pamphlet (layout; booklets; governing policies, Service Rules, the outdoor advertising medium, Channel of Communication; American Restaurant Magazine for 1955 Aug.)]
    - Structural Design Booklet--Snow Load Studies, 1952 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Structural Design--Timber Construction Booklet, 1938 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Structure Trends, 1984 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Suppliers' Conference, 1955 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Supplier: Rennous Kleinle Division, 1931-1932 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
      [Rennous Kleinle Division (Pittsburgh Plate Glass), Baltimore, 1931-1932]
    - Suppliers, undated (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Supply Department Bulletins, 1928-1929 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
    - Survey of Bulletin Standards, 1951 and undated (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
      [Handwritten spreadsheets; recap of replies to Painted Display Questionnaire]
    - Tiffin A-Frame Panel Erection Photos, 1948 (Box PS7 -Letter Size)
  - Illumination (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Backlights, undated (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Fiber Optics, 1984 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Fluorescent Lighting, 1958 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - ...Illumination Control in the Defense of the... United States, 1954 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1960, undated (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Painted Bulletin Lighting, 1983 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Solar Power, 1983 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Spectacolor, [1985] (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Standards, 1958-1959, 2 folders (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Tele-Spot/ Thomas Towers, 1973 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
      [Spiral album of images of Tele-Spot signs; Tele-Spot Display Systems; report by Information Concepts concerning standards for reflective disk changeable messages systems (Tele-Spot), systems overview, technology, and safety]
    - Tele-Spot/ Thomas Towers, 1975 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Video Billboards, 1984 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Animated Cut Outs, 1954 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - American Standards Association Conference of Staff Executives, 1945-1946 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - American Standards Association Standards Mark Committee, 1950 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
    - Plastics, 1944-1953 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
      [Flammability test; Fiberglas trim test program; article; mechanical properties of laminated plastics; plastic buckling; booklet-Plexiglas]
    - Standard and Junior Panels, 1944-1954, 2 folders (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
      [Association Standard and Junior Poster Panels (standards and codes; certification of copyright registration; molding and trim design; Ad Andy; correspondence about blueprints but no blueprints; report of meeting at French Lick 1945)]
    - Standard and Junior Panels, Karl Ghaster Correspondence, 1938-1946 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
      [Post-war planning board; structures; experimental model infra-red dryer; Raymond Loewy Associates; super-wood; Notre Dame; post-war plant redevelopment; W. Rex Bell; illumination; frames; cost of conversion; photos; Canadian Poster News 1944]
    - Standard and Poster Panels, 1939-1945, Folder 1 of 3 (Box PS8 -Letter Size)
      [Meeting French Lick 1945; copyrights; patent for framing and blanking means; post-war planning board; correspondence about blueprints but no blueprints; Raymond Loewy; Rex Bell; post-war planning board; porcelain molding]
    - Standard and Poster Panels, 1944-1948, Folders 2-3 of 3 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Standardization, 1946-1951 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
      [Booklets-Standards are Your Business, Voluntary Standards, Legal Aspects of Standardization by John F. Sonnet at 13th annual meeting; reprint-Legal Aspects of Standardization and Simplification]
  - Patents
    - Association Structures, 1927-1945 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
      [Association Structures 1928 (Vego cloth-Freeman-Lee patent; others)]
    - Association Structures, 1929-1934 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927-1952 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
  - Poles and Anchorage
    - Anchorage and Embedment, 1940-1947, 2 folders (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Anchorage Testing and Rutledge Report, 1944-1947 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
      [ Dr. P.C. Rutledge, Technological Institute, Northwestern University, Evanston, Ill.]
    - Anchoring to Rock, 1953 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Anchor Test Project- Purdue University (1939-40), 1939-1947 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Effect of Anchorage Embedment, Size, and Shape, 1947 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Information Bulletin...on Anchorage specifications for...Standard A-Frame Poster Panels, 1947 July (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940-1953, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
    - Pole Stability Research, 1932-1948 (Box PS9 -Letter Size)
      [Final Report. A.R.F. Project No. K-655 Study of Poster Pole Configurations, 1959]
    - Poster-Pole Studies, 1959 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Reports of Field and Laboratory Tests on the Stability of Posts Against Lateral Loads, 1940-1947 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
      [Report on Research, Foundation and Anchorage for Cantilever Type 1947 Structures ( Notre Dame-report of the effect of anchorage embedment and shape on the deflection of cantilever type backstructure uprights for outdoor advertising structures)]
    - Report of Field and Laboratory Tests on the Stability of Posts Against Lateral Loads, 1947 and undated (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Resistance of Soil Anchors for Outdoor Advertising Structures, 1940 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Single Pole Construction, 1971 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Single Pole Construction-Unipole, undated (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Soil, 1940-1951 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
      [Soil (correspondence; reprint- Essentials of Soil-Cement Testing and Construction; reprint-- Soil-cement Construction Details; list of publications of Gregory P. Tachebotarioff, Princeton; conference on soil mechanics and its applications; article- Static Load Tests for Bearing Piles)]
    - Soil Cement, 1951 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Soil Studies, 1951 and undated (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Stability of Posts Against Lateral Loads, Notre Dame Report, 1948 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Wind Forces on Structures, Research, 1951-1952 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Wooden Pole vs. Steel Cost Analysis, 1963 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
  - Posters and Paper
    - 24 and 30 Sheet Posters, 1954, 1956 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Bleed Poster, undated (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Coca-Cola Flagging Posters, 1943-1946 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Flagging-Member Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Flagging Problem, undated (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
      [ To Cut Down the Flagging Poster Problem by Charles Keesling]
    - Horizontal Sections Manufacturer- Tiffin Metal (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Letter to Chairman's Advisory Committee-re: Poster Collation, 1961 (Box PS10 -Letter Size)
    - Lithography Cutout, 1957-1958 (Box PS11 -Letter Size)
    - Paper, 1947-1949 (Box PS11 -Letter Size)
      [Blanking paper; paste cooking equipment; post-war paper; lattice]
    - Paper and Posting Difficulties, 1935-1946 (Box PS11 -Letter Size)
      [Correspondence of H.E. Fisk-memos, letters, photos from Wenatchee, Washington, 1941 Mar.]
    - Paper Reclamation, 1942-1943 (Box PS11 -Letter Size)
      [Scrap paper baler]
    - Paper Salvage, 1944 (Box PS11 -Letter Size)
    - Paste, 1940-1953 (Box PS11 -Letter Size)